Ohto Ai...
What are you doing in a place like this?
Walking.
This late at night?
Oh... a dream?
You don't like dreams?
Would you prefer reality?
The first time's free.
After that, bring your wallet.
How much?
Don't worry. I know you'll like it.
It's a special capsule machine, after all.
Special how?
It has the thing you want in it.
I don't really want anything.
Don't lie.
Of course you do.
A friend.
It wasn't a dream.
I wonder if I should keep it cold.
But if it's alive, maybe I should warm it up.
It's hard.
Oh, it might end up as a boiled egg.
Can I crack it?
Actually, should I crack it?
I'll drop off my bag. You go on ahead.
The usual place?
Yeah.
Ai! Your teacher is here.
There's no need to force her to get up, ma'am.
I just brought this week's printouts.
I'm so sorry.
You're always so kind.
Oh no, it's nothing.
I wonder what's in it.
I'm just stopping by to check on her on my way home.
I'll try going back there tomorrow.
I'm going out.
Huh?
This is...
What am I doing at school?
You're overdoing it.
Any less and she won't get the message.
In that case, I'll add a bunch more.
Whoa, brutal! Who's overdoing it now?
All of you at school today, a question:
What should you do if someone
in your class is being bullied?
You got it! The right answer is:
Pretend not to see!
Ohto Ai.
Break the Egg.
The Egg?
The Wonder Egg.
You mean this?
Quickly, break it.
But it's so hard, I can't crack it.
Break it now!
Break it!
Shut up!
You're good at this.
Damn it. Why'd you break it in a place like this?
If you're done, leave.
Okay.
Did she have to put it like that?
I hate her attitude.
Just ask normally.
I said yes, though.
Stand up!
Okay!
Let's run!
Huh?
What's that?
Oh, um, uh...
We need to run.
What are they?!
You ought to know!
They're Seeno Evils!
What's that?!
No idea!
Stand up!
This way!
Wait up!
Is this where my liver is?
Am I going to be okay?!
Let's go!
Huh?
Hurry up!
It's a dream.
A bad dream.
Show me your cut.
Huh?
Hurry.
It's gone.
Mine don't disappear.
This is a dream to you, but to me, it's reality.
Anyway, we'll keep running until the bell rings.
There's nothing to be scared of.
They only come after me.
Plus, you're immortal in this world.
As long as your eyes and heart are okay.
Does that really count as immortal?
Well, I guess not.
Oh, why is this happening to me?
Because you bought the Egg.
I didn't buy it.
They said the first one is free.
Yeah. Nothing costs more than a free gift, huh?
It's not funny.
So, you've got no friends.
I don't not have them; I don't need them.
No way.
It's true.
You wouldn't have broken the Egg if it were.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
I didn't have any either.
No way.
It's the truth.
I guess I did have superficial ones.
Friends who would chime in,
"Totally!
Oh, I know! Adorable!"
But I didn't have a best friend.
Thinking back on it, best friends matter a lot.
You break up with boyfriends,
but best friends are forever, right?
I guess so.
You had a boyfriend?
Did you?
I asked first.
Okay, how about we answer on "go"?
Sure.
Ready, go.
No fair!
Same to you.
Huh?
Hm?
Let's go.
Sorry.
Why apologize?
It's their fault.
I'm sorry!
It's true. They don't attack me.
They don't... attack me.
Hm?
Koito?
I'm Nagase Koito.
Please be friends with me, everyone.
All right, Nagase, take the seat next to Ohto.
Okay.
Let's walk home together.
Huh?
What do you mean, "Huh"?
That hurts.
It's nice and quiet here, huh?
What's that?
A game.
Do you like games?
Kind of.
Hmm.
What game?
Ohto?
U-Umm,
I don't think you should hang out with me.
Why not?
B-Because I'm ugly!
What?
You're not even a little ugly.
You've got big, round eyes.
Your haircut?
Why do you hide this one?
Where's your umbrella?
I forgot it.
And your bag?
Ai?
I forgot it.
Is something wrong?
It's nothing!
Ai, a friend is here to see you.
She's not my friend. I don't have friends.
You forgot these. I came to return them.
Thanks.
That's called heterochromia, right?
When your irises are different colors.
It's common in cats and dogs.
It's mysterious.
You shouldn't hide it.
I get bullied for it.
Always.
It's pretty.
Be my friend.
Let's be best friends.
No?
I... want to, but...
But?
If we could, I'd be happy.
Me, too.
It's my fault.
Because I betrayed you.
Even though you were the first friend I ever made.
Koito.
But... But I almost made it until the bell rang!
I'm sick of this.
Stay away!
Crosswalks are still scary
even when you move with the crowd.
I'm done pretending not to see!
Now I'm mad!
I'm Saijo Kurumi.
Ohto Ai.
Ai... I guess this is goodbye.
Huh?
Don't forget me.
Too bad.
Only you get saved.
But you have to cheer up
if you want your best friend back.
Huh?
She's a little warm.
Because I protected Kurumi?
Hey, if I protect a bunch more people,
will Koito come back to life?
She will, right?!
Ai! Breakfast is ready!
Thank you.
The weather is lovely today, so don't spend it all in bed.
I hung up the laundry to dry, so take it in this afternoon.
Oh.
Oh, would you look at the time.
I'm immortal there, but...
I have a meeting this morning, so I've got to go now.
Lunch is...
What on earth...
I don't know. I have no idea.
Maybe she snuck out last night and...
Please, stay strong.
Koito...
Hi there. How are your injuries?
I'll manage.
And your wallet?
I brought it.
How many rescues to bring Koito back?
That, I can't say.
If I protect more at once, will it go that much faster?
You're a greedy idiot, huh?
If you can't protect them, you won't make it either.
Koito!
Besides, your enemies won't always be so easy.
They're just Seeno Evils.
A disorderly mob.
Whoa!
What happened to Kurumi?
She's just like your best friend.
She's a sculpture in some world.
And unless her friends go to that
world, she'll stay that way forever.
Did Kurumi kill herself, too?
No comment.
♪ No comment. ♪
Welcome.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Acca.
The one to your left is Ura-Acca.
Hey.
Hey...
There's someone ahead of you.
Wait a moment.
Okay.
Wait, I'm not the only one?
That girl...
Wow.
Yes, we're always worried about her—
She's got an amazing figure!
Oh, that.
To be continued.